beachbodyondemand.com 2018-09-07

# Privacy Policy | Beachbody On Demand

## For U.S. and Canadian residents

 ** _Last updated_ : August 1, 2016**

Beachbody, LLC (applicable to our U.S. audience) and Team Beachbody Canada, LP (applicable to our Canadian audience), together with our parent companies, affiliates, and subsidiaries (collectively, “ **Beachbody** ”, “ **us** ”, “ **we** ” or “ **our** ”) know that you care about how your information is used and shared, and we appreciate the trust you place in us that we will do so carefully and sensibly. We provide you with this Privacy Policy because we want you to know how we may collect, use, share and keep information about you, and the choices that are available to you. 

Please don’t hesitate to contact us at any time if you have any questions regarding the contents in this Privacy Policy by e-mailing _[Privacy@Beachbody.com](mailto:Privacy@beachbody.com)_.

 **When Does this Privacy Policy Apply?**

This Privacy Policy applies whenever we collect personal information from or about you when you access or use any of our websites, applications, content, streaming services, products, goods, equipment, services, promotions, software, technology and any other materials (collectively, “ **Beachbody Services** ”), or when you contact us in any manner.

 **What Information Is Collected From You Through Beachbody Services?**

The information we receive from you helps us personalize and continually improve our business. Here are the general types of personal information (and sensitive personal information) we (and certain third parties) may gather: 

  * **_Information You Give Us_** : We receive, store and process personal information you provide to us when you purchase or use the Beachbody Services, set up a Team Beachbody account, enter information on our websites or message boards, communicate with us over phone, e-mail or otherwise, use our applications on mobile or connected devices, use our streaming services, take our surveys, participate in any promotion, interact with our social media presence, or in any other way.

  *  _ **Examples of Information You Give Us**_ : This includes without limitation your name, shipping, billing, and/or business addresses; location information; phone number; e-mail address; username and password information; credit or other payment card information; gender; date of birth; and survey response data. If you sign up as a Team Beachbody Coach, we may also collect your social security/social insurance or other similar identification number and bank account information in order to remit any commission payments you may have earned. If you apply to join our Affiliate Program, we may also collect information about your business, such as your (or your organization's) name, e-mail address, street address, telephone number, tax identification number, and information about your website (e.g., the URL, the number of unique users and page views, the demographics of your user base, etc.). To help track your workout activity, Beachbody may send and receive data to and from Apple’s Healthkit Application if you enabled this feature.

We may also collect other types of information that you provide to us to help you achieve your health and wellness goals, such as your: 

  * _physical information_ (e.g., weight, waist, hip and bicep measurements, etc.); 
  * _food and nutritional information_ (e.g., types of food and beverages consumed, and any related caloric, fat, fiber, cholesterol and other information); 
  * _metabolic information_ (e.g., caloric and fat burn through exercise, and other related information); 
  * _fitness and activity information_ (e.g., the types and number of workouts you may be using, workout and activity tracking, hours exercised, etc.); and 
  * _general feedback_ (e.g., content you post on our message boards, or information you submit about our products, goods or services). 

**_Information We Automatically Receive_** : We automatically receive and store certain technical information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many other websites, we use “cookies” to enhance your experience on our websites as described below, which allows us to obtain certain information when your web browser accesses any of our websites. 

**_Examples of Information We Automatically Receive_** : This includes without limitation your Internet protocol (IP) address (the number used to identify your computer or modem to the Internet, which can potentially identify your location and Internet Service Provider), browser or device type, version and time zone setting, operating system and platform; information about your activities on our websites, including the Uniform Resource Locator (URL) from which you came to our websites and the URLs that you visited on our websites; cookie identifier; products you viewed or searched for; the phone number you used to call us; pixel tag data as described below; and purchase history. During some visits to our websites, we may use software tools such as JavaScript to measure and collect session information, including page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), and methods used to browse away from the page. We may also collect technical information to help us identify your device for fraud prevention and diagnostic purposes.

  *  ** _Mobile and Connected Device Information_** : When you download, install or use our applications through mobile or connected devices, we may receive information about your device and may access your camera, microphone, or other device services or hardware. Some devices may allow you to opt-out of this collection or access, and in those cases, you may be able to subsequently stop the collection or access. Please review your device settings for more information. 
  * **_Examples of Mobile Information_** : This includes without limitation unique identifiers for your device, device and usage information, precise geolocation information (if you enabled this feature), carrier provider, and the types of mobile devices and operating systems accessing the application.
  *  ** _Information We Obtain From Other Sources_** : We may receive information about you from other sources, including from third party vendors, services and commercially available sources (such as data aggregators and public databases). We may also collect information that you publicly post on our social media pages, such as our Facebook®, Instagram®, and Twitter® pages. In addition, we may combine information you give us with other information from Beachbody sources, communications and transactions. Where permitted by law, we combine this information received from other sources, including from social media websites, with information you give us and information that we collect automatically about you.
  *  ** _Examples of Information We Obtain From Other Sources:_** This includes without limitation, information that you provide to our vendors; updated credit card number and expiration dates from your bank or credit card company which we use to keep our records current and service you better; updated delivery and address information from our carriers or other third parties which we use to keep our records current, process orders, deliver your next purchase, and service you better; account information which we use to validate access to your accounts with us; transactional data from third party purchases; demographic and profile data; social media posts, such as your likes, interests, feedback, preferences, pictures, comments, suggestions, opinions, and complaints; information we may receive from your Team Beachbody Coach (if applicable); information that you provide through our e-mail and text message campaigns; information about products or services purchased from other companies. 

**How Does Beachbody Use the Information It Collects?**

Beachbody may use the information provided above in various ways, including without limitation, to: 

  * Process and fulfill your requests or orders for any Beachbody Services, and verify your identity and/or location to allow access to your accounts (such as your Team Beachbody or Beachbody On Demand account); 

  * Communicate with you about your orders or any inquiries you may have submitted to us; 

  * Tell you about new products, goods or services, including if you started a transaction with us and provided your information, but did not finalize your order;
  * Service and manage your accounts, or contact you about your accounts;
  * Address a problem or issue affecting your use of any Beachbody Services, or to inquire about or verify information concerning a transaction;
  * Assist you with your health and wellness goals, such as providing you with advice and feedback on your goals, and connecting you with individuals who share your interests; 
  * Improve any Beachbody Services and related advertising or materials;
  * Enhance and personalize your Beachbody experience on any Beachbody Services, and control the frequency of advertisements to your device; 
  * Target advertising or promotions that may be of interest to you, such as e-mails, direct mail, banner ads, splash ads (ads that appear as you sign in or out of your online accounts) or promotions based on your demographic profile, interests, or location; 
  * Send you emails and other communications about Beachbody's or any of our business partners' products or services that we think you may find useful, or to see if you are interested in participating in surveys, market research or other inquiries; 
  * Administer contests, promotions, events, surveys or other features; 
  * Improve, personalize, and optimize your website browsing and mobile application experiences by examining which parts of our website you visit or which aspect of our mobile applications you find most useful, and to improve existing or develop new products and services;
  * Operate, improve and maintain our Beachbody Services, including for data analysis, such as user behavior and trends, and diagnose problems with our server and administer our websites;
  * Assist us in taking data security precautions and to engage in fraud prevention, detection, and remediation;
  * Carry out other purposes which are disclosed to you and to which you consent; 
  * Undertake statistical analysis and research, and for demographic profiling purposes; or
  * Comply with applicable international, federal, state, provincial/territorial and local laws, directives, rules, regulations, and ordinances; civil, criminal or regulatory investigations; or other legal requirements, such as court orders.

 ** _Apple HealthKit Data_** : Beachbody will not use or share health data collected through Apple HealthKit for marketing purposes.

 **What About Cookies, Pixel Tags and Third Party Tracking Tools?**

  *  ** _Cookies_** **:** Like almost every company, Beachbody and others use a technology commonly known as a "cookie", which is a small data file our server places on your computer or mobile device to recognize your device and provide personalized features and advertisements. Cookies are widely used by website owners in order to make their websites work, or to work more efficiently, as well as to provide reporting information. Through cookies, we are able to collect information that we use to improve our websites and mobile applications, improve your overall experience on them, and personalize your experiences and advertisements. For example, through cookies, we can keep count of return visits to our website or our advertisers' or partners' websites, collect and report on aggregate statistical information, authenticate your login credentials, and manage multiple instances of our websites in a single browser. We may also collect other data through cookies, such as the page or website that referred you to us, the date and time you visited us, and your current IP address. The cookies we place on your hard drive are known as "first-party cookies" and any cookies placed by third parties are called “third party cookies.” Third party cookies enable third party features or functionality to be provided on or through the website (e.g., advertising, interactive content and analytics). The parties that set these third party cookies can recognize your computer both when it visits the website in question and also when it visits certain other websites. 
  * **_Disabling Cookies:_ **Most major web browsers provide users with the option to accept or reject cookies. Opting out of the use of cookies to deliver targeted advertising relies on information in the unique cookies placed on your web browser by our partners, so if you delete cookies, use a different device, or change web browsers, you may need to opt out again. Please note that if you use your browser settings to block all cookies you may not be able to access parts of our or others' websites. The “Help” feature on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. Additionally, you can disable or delete similar data used by browser add-ons, such as Flash cookies, by changing the add-on's settings or visiting the website of its manufacturer. Since cookies allow you to take advantage of some of our essential features, we recommend that you leave them turned on. For instance, if you block or otherwise reject our cookies, you may not be able to utilize certain features on our websites, such as adding items to your shopping cart, proceeding to checkout, or using services that require you to sign in.
  *  ** _Pixel Tags_** : We also collect information through the use of "pixel tags" on our websites and in e-mail messages we may send to you that may be placed by us or third parties with whom we partner. “Pixels,” also known as "Web beacons," are tiny graphic files or code snippets, not visible to the human eye, that can be included in HTML-encoded e-mail messages and web pages. When such a message is opened in an HTML-capable e-mail program, the recipient's computer or device will communicate with our server to retrieve the pixel tag file, allowing us to record and store, along with the recipient's e-mail address, the date and time the recipient viewed the e-mail message, the fact that the recipient's e-mail client is capable of receiving HTML-encoded e-mail, and other standard logging information. The pixel tag may also see or read cookies. Beachbody may use pixel tags in order to measure and understand traffic better, improve site performance, track visitor behavior to improve user experience, and for tracking promotional and marketing campaign response, among others. You can disable the pixel tag feature by changing the settings on your e-mail client to prevent the automatic downloading of images, changing your browser settings to omit images, disabling Javascript, or there are commercial software packages available that can omit pixel tags and most advertisements.
  *  ** _Behavioral Advertising on Third Party Websites_** : We also work with third parties that use tracking technologies on our websites and on other websites in order to provide and track tailored advertisements on our behalf and on behalf of other advertisers across the Internet. These third party partners may place or recognize a unique cookie on your hard drive. They may help Beachbody place first party cookies from our servers, or third party cookies from their own or other third party servers. Beachbody and our advertisers and third party advertising partners may use cookies in order to collect information about you, which may include how many times you have seen an ad or whether you have interacted with an ad. We and our partners may also use cookies to provide you with interest-based or behavioral advertising. The use of third-party cookies is not covered by this Privacy Policy as these third parties are subject to their own privacy policies. For more information about this practice and to understand your options for many of our advertising partners, please visit _[http://www.youradchoices.com](http://www.youradchoices.com/)_ (U.S.), _[http://www.youradchoices.ca](http://www.youradchoices.ca/)_ (Canada) or the Network Advertising Initiative at _[www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/)_. If you choose to opt-out of behavioral advertising using these cookies, you will still be served with advertisements on the Internet, but it may not be tailored to your interests. Most major web browsers provide users with the option to accept or reject third party cookies. Opting out relies on information in the unique cookies placed on your web browser by our partners, so if you delete cookies, use a different device, or change web browsers, you may need to opt out again. 
  * **_Do Not Track Signals_** : Some web browsers offer a “Do Not Track” signal that is a HTTP header field indicating your preference regarding tracking or cross-site user tracking. Like many other websites and online services, we do not currently alter our practices when we receive Do Not Track signals or other mechanisms that provide consumers the ability to exercise choice regarding the collection of personally identifiable information about an individual consumer’s online activities over time and across third-party websites or online services, as there is no consensus among industry participants as to what "Do Not Track" means in this context. To find out more about "Do Not Track," you may wish to visit _<http://www.allaboutdnt.com/>__._

 **Does Beachbody Share the Information and Data it Receives?**

We value the trust our customers place in us to safeguard their personal information. We share personal information we collect with your consent and as described below: 

  * **_Third-Party Service Providers_** : We utilize third party companies and individuals to perform business functions on our behalf to better serve you. For example, we use third parties to help us make our products and services available to you, fulfill orders you may have placed, process credit card payments, provide customer service, ship postal mail, deliver your packages, conduct market research or information analysis, manage promotions, and contact you in connection with various Beachbody Services. In these instances, we may need to provide your information to these third parties for such purposes. 
  * **_Assignment to a Team Beachbody Coach and/or Master Trainer_** : To maximize the benefits of our products and services, we assign an independent Team Beachbody Coach (a “ **Coach** ”) to all customers who agree to a Team Beachbody Club membership or who consent to be contacted by a Coach. Your assigned Coach is available to assist you in understanding and using the products you ordered, and help give you the motivation you need to help you achieve your fitness goals. To help you both get in contact, your assigned Coach will receive access to certain information you provided during your purchase process, such as your name, address, phone number, e-mail address and the names of the products you purchased. Your Coach may contact you to offer support, and provide general information and marketing materials. Please note that Beachbody will never provide your assigned Coach your credit or debit card information or, if you provided it, your Social Security number/Social Insurance number. If you joined Beachbody LIVE!, we may provide certain basic information to the Master Trainer assigned to train you during your training, such as your name, e-mail address and phone number. 
  * **_Related Companies; Third Party Offers_** : Beachbody occasionally partners with third parties to learn more about our customers so we can service you better or offer products or services that we feel may be useful to you (" **Related Company** "). In such case, we may disclose to a Related Company certain information, such as your name, e-mail, billing or shipping address, products purchased and price. If you request information from a Related Company, we may disclose additional information such as your e-mail address, phone number and other contact information, so the Related Company can provide you with the information you requested. If you purchased a product or service from a Related Company, we will also disclose your credit card information so they can complete your purchase. We may disclose aggregated, de-identified information to Related Companies: (i) so the Related Companies can provide you with advertisements tailored to your interests; (ii) for statistical analysis, research, and demographic profiling purposes; and (iii) to support our business and improve our mission to help our customers achieve their health and wellness goals.
  *  ** _Protection of Beachbody and Others_** : We may share your information, including personally identifiable information, in order to: (i) protect or defend the legal rights or property of Beachbody, or the legal rights of our customers, Coaches, business partners, employees, agents, and contractors; (ii) protect the safety and security of our customers, Coaches or members of the public, including acting in urgent circumstances; (iii) detect and protect against fraud and identity theft or to conduct risk management; (iv) comply with laws, legal process, or legal requests from any governmental or regulatory body; or (v) to enforce or apply our website Terms and Conditions and/or other agreements.
  *  ** _De-identified Data Disclosures_** : We may also disclose non-identifying transaction information to third parties for the purpose of accounting and record keeping. We may also disclose aggregated, de-identified user data or non-personal information with business partners, advertisers, and others.

 **What About Third-Party and Advertisers’ Services?**

At various points and pages on our websites or mobile applications, you may be able to access or utilize services offered by or in conjunction with third parties. This includes services in connection with third-party "social media" and other sites that would allow personal information to be transferred to such third parties (for example, Facebook Connect), Coaches, and others. 

These third parties have separate data collection and privacy practices independent from ours, so please review their privacy policies to understand your rights. For this reason, Beachbody cannot be responsible for their policies or activities. Please contact those third parties directly if you have questions about their privacy practices. 

**How Secure is Information About Me?**

Beachbody has implemented and uses reasonable security measures designed to help prevent the loss and unauthorized access of your information. Despite these efforts, no security measures are perfect or impenetrable, and no method of data transmission can be guaranteed against interception or to be absolutely secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or our online services. If you suspect a website or mobile application is pretending to be that of Beachbody’s (also known as “spoofing”), do not enter any personal information, but please let us know by e-mailing _[CyberSecurity@Beachbody.com](mailto:CyberSecurity@beachbody.com)_. Personal information may be accessed by persons within our organization, or our third party service providers, who require such access to carry out the purposes indicated above, or such other purposes as may be permitted or required by the applicable law. Personal Information we collect is maintained in the United States. 

**What Happens to My Information if Beachbody is Sold to or Merges With Another Company?**

As we continue to develop and grow our business or in the unlikely event of a bankruptcy, we might sell one or more of our assets, subsidiaries or business units. In such transactions, customer information is typically one of the transferred business assets. 

**Users Based Outside of the USA; Transfer of Personal Information**

Like most websites and businesses, Beachbody’s websites may be accessed by an international audience. By visiting our websites, using our applications, and/or providing us with any data, you agree we may collect, process, use, and store your personal information as discussed herein, outside your resident jurisdiction (such as the U.S. or Canada). Our Related Companies and third party service providers may also be located outside of your jurisdiction. As a result, this information may be subject to access requests from governments, courts, or law enforcement in those jurisdictions according to laws in those jurisdictions. Please note that U.S. law and those of other countries where your information may be stored and processed may offer different levels of protection for your information than your home country. We will take all reasonable steps to ensure that such personal information is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

 **How Can I Access or Update My Information?**

We want to be sure your personal information is kept accurate and complete, and for this reason we ask that you inform us in the event of any changes to your information. If you provided your information _directly to Beachbody_ , you may access or update certain personal information by calling our Customer Service at (800) 470-7870 or logging into your Team Beachbody account if you created one. When calling Customer Service, please have your e-mail address and order information available. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to respond to your request to access or update your information. Please note that certain access may be subject to a fee. 

**Your Privacy Choices: Opt-Out**

  *  ** _Marketing_** : We offer you various ways to opt-out of receiving certain communications from us. If you would like to opt-out of receiving e-mail marketing communications from us, you may click the “Unsubscribe” link found at the bottom of Beachbody marketing e-mails that we send and follow the easy instructions to opt-out, or you may click the “Preferences” links to update your e-mail settings. If you would like to opt-out of receiving marketing phone calls, you can inform the agent with whom you speak that you would like to be placed on Beachbody’s “Do Not Call” list. If you would like to opt-out of any Beachbody text message campaign, please follow the instructions provided when you opt-in to the campaign; typically, responding “STOP” to your specific short code will opt you out of the campaign for which you signed up.
  *  ** _Online Advertising_** : To learn some of the ways that you can opt-out of targeted online advertising, see the section above titled “What About Cookies, Pixel Tags and Third Party Tracking Tools?" for more information. 

**Changes to This Privacy Policy**

Beachbody may modify this Privacy Policy at any time effective upon its posting on our websites. Your continued business relationship with us, or use of any of our Beachbody Services after the changes are posted constitutes your acceptance of any changes, both with regard to information we have previously collected from you and information we may collect from you in the future. 

**Notice to California Residents - Your California Privacy Rights (As Provided by California Civil Code section 1798.83).**

A California resident who has provided Personal Data, as defined under California Civil Code section 1798.83, to a business with whom he/she has established a business relationship for personal, family, or household purposes (a “ **California Customer** ”) may request information about whether the business has disclosed personal information to any third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes. In general, if the business has made such a disclosure of Personal Data, upon receipt of a request by a California Customer, the business is required to provide a list of all third parties to whom Personal Data was disclosed in the preceding calendar year, as well as a list of the categories of Personal Data that were disclosed. California Customers may request further information about our compliance with this law by e-mailing _[Privacy@Beachbody.com](mailto:Privacy@beachbody.com)_. Please note that we are required to respond to one request per California Customer each year, and we are not required to respond to requests made by means other than through this e-mail address.

 **Contacting Beachbody**

Please feel free to share any comments, concerns, complaints, or questions with us: 

Chief Legal Officer

Beachbody, LLC – Attn: Legal Department

3301 Exposition Blvd.

Santa Monica, CA 90404

or email us: _[Privacy@Beachbody.com](mailto:Privacy@beachbody.com)_

**POLITIQUE DE CONFIDENTIALITÉ**

 **Pour les résidents des É.-U. et du Canada**

 _Dernière mise à jour  :_ 1er août 2016

Beachbody, LLC (applicable à notre audience des États-Unis) et Team Beachbody Canada, LP (applicable à notre audience du Canada), en collaboration avec nos sociétés mères, sociétés affiliées et filiales (collectivement, «  **Beachbody**  », «  **nous**  », ou « **notre**  ») savent que vous vous souciez de la façon dont vos renseignements sont utilisés et partagés et nous vous sommes reconnaissants de la confiance que vous nous accordez pour que nous le fassions avec soin et judicieusement. Nous vous fournissons cette politique de confidentialité parce que nous voulons que vous sachiez la façon dont nous pouvons recueillir, utiliser, partager et conserver des renseignements vous concernant et les choix qui sont à votre disposition. 

Si vous avez des questions concernant le contenu de cette politique de confidentialité, veuillez ne pas hésiter à communiquer avec nous par courriel en tout temps à _[Privacy@Beachbody.com](mailto:Privacy@beachbody.com)_. 

**Application de la politique de confidentialité**

Cette politique de confidentialité s'applique chaque fois que nous recueillons des renseignements personnels à votre sujet lorsque vous accédez ou utilisez l'un de nos sites Web, des applications, du contenu, des services de diffusion en continu, des produits, des biens, des équipements, des services, des promotions, des logiciels, de la technologie et tout autre matériel (collectivement, «  **services de Beachbody**  ») ou lorsque vous communiquez avec nous d'une façon quelconque.

 **Renseignements recueillis auprès de vous par les services de Beachbody**

Les renseignements que nous recevons de votre part nous aident à personnaliser et à améliorer continuellement notre entreprise. Voici les types de renseignements personnels (et des renseignements personnels sensibles) que nous (et certains tiers) pouvons recueillir : 

  * **_Renseignements que vous nous donnez  :_** Nous recevons, sauvegardons et traitons les renseignements personnels que vous nous fournissez lorsque vous achetez ou utilisez les services de Beachbody, créez un compte Team Beachbody, entrez des renseignements sur nos sites ou babillards électroniques, communiquez avec nous par téléphone, courriel ou autrement, utilisez nos applications sur des appareils mobiles ou raccordés physiquement, utilisez nos services de diffusion en continu, répondez à nos sondages, participez à toute promotion, interagissez avec nous sur les médias sociaux ou de toute autre manière.

  *  ** _Exemples de renseignements que vous nous donnez  :_** Cela inclut, sans s'y limiter, vos nom, adresse d'expédition, de facturation, et d'entreprise ; les renseignements sur l'emplacement ; le numéro de téléphone ; l'adresse de courriel ; le nom d'utilisateur et le mot de passe ; les renseignements de crédit ou autres renseignements de carte de paiement ; le genre ; la date de naissance ; et des données de réponses aux sondages. Si vous vous inscrivez en tant que Coach Team Beachbody, nous pouvons également recueillir votre numéro de sécurité sociale/d’assurance sociale ou tout autre numéro d'identification similaire et les renseignements de compte bancaire en vue de verser les paiements de commissions que vous avez gagnées. Si vous présentez une demande pour vous joindre à notre programme d'affiliation, nous pouvons également recueillir des renseignements sur votre entreprise, tels que vos nom, adresse de courriel, adresse postale, numéro de téléphone, numéro d'identification aux fins de l’impôt et des renseignements sur votre site Web (par exemple, adresse URL, nombre d'utilisateurs uniques et de pages vues, les données démographiques de votre base d'utilisateurs, etc.) ou ceux de votre entreprise. Pour faciliter le suivi de votre séances d'entraînement, Beachbody peut envoyer et recevoir des données vers et depuis l'application Healthkit d'Apple si vous avez activé cette fonctionnalité.

Nous pouvons également recueillir d'autres types de renseignements que vous nous fournissez pour vous aider à atteindre vos objectifs de santé et de bien-être, tels que : 

  * _information d’ordre physique_ (par exemple, le poids, la taille, les mesures des hanches et des biceps, etc.) ; 

  * _la nourriture et l'information nutritionnelle_ (par exemple, les types d'aliments et de boissons consommés, et renseignements reliés aux calories, lipides, fibres, cholestérol et autres renseignements) ; 
  * _des informations métaboliques_ (par exemple, la consommation de calories et la graisse brûlée grâce à l'exercice et autres renseignements connexes) ; 
  * _des informations sur le conditionnement physique et les activités_ (par exemple, les types et le nombre de séances d'entraînement que vous faites, le suivi de l'entraînement et des activités, les heures d'exercices, etc.) ; et 
  * _des_ _commentaires généraux_ (par exemple, le contenu que vous publiez sur nos babillards électroniques ou des renseignements que vous soumettez sur nos produits, biens ou services). 

**_Renseignements que nous recevons automatiquement  :_** Nous recevons et sauvegardons certains renseignements techniques chaque fois que vous interagissez avec nous. Par exemple, comme beaucoup d'autres sites Web, nous utilisons des « témoins » pour améliorer votre expérience sur nos sites Web tel que décrit ci-dessous, ce qui nous permet d'obtenir certains renseignements lorsque votre navigateur Web accède à l'un de nos sites. 

**_Exemples de renseignements que nous recevons automatiquement  :_** Ceci inclut, sans s'y limiter, votre adresse de protocole Internet (IP) (le numéro utilisé pour identifier votre ordinateur ou un modem à Internet), ce qui peut potentiellement identifier votre emplacement et fournisseur de services Internet, le navigateur et le type d'appareil, la version et les paramètres de fuseau horaire et le système ainsi que la plate-forme d'exploitation ; des renseignements sur vos activités sur nos sites Web, y compris les adresses de localisateur de ressources uniforme (URL) à partir desquelles vous avez accédé à nos sites Web et les adresses URL que vous avez visitées sur nos sites Web ; l'identificateur de témoin ; les produits que vous avez consultés ou cherchés ; le numéro de téléphone que vous avez utilisé pour nous appeler ; données de pixels invisibles tel que décrit ci-dessous et l'historique d'achat. Au cours des visites sur nos sites Web, nous pouvons utiliser des outils logiciels tels que JavaScript afin de mesurer et recueillir des renseignements de session, y compris les temps de réponse des pages, les erreurs de téléchargement, la durée des visites à certaines pages, les renseignements d'interaction sur des pages (tels que le défilement, les clics et les pointages de souris) ainsi que les méthodes utilisées pour naviguer à l'extérieur de la page. Nous pouvons également recueillir des renseignements techniques pour nous aider à identifier votre appareil pour la prévention de la fraude et à des fins de diagnostic.

  *  ** _Renseignements sur les appareils mobiles ou raccordés physiquement_** _  :_ Lorsque vous téléchargez, installez ou utilisez nos applications sur des appareils mobiles ou raccordés physiquement, nous pouvons recevoir des renseignements sur votre appareil et accéder à la caméra, au microphone ou autres services ou matériel de votre appareil. Certains appareils peuvent vous permettre de refuser cette collecte de renseignements ou accès, et dans ces cas, vous pourriez être en mesure d'arrêter subséquemment la collecte de renseignements ou l'accès. Veuillez vérifier les paramètres de votre appareil pour plus d'informations. 
  * **_Exemples de renseignements pour l'utilisation mobile  :_** Ceci inclut, sans s'y limiter, des identificateurs uniques pour l'appareil, les renseignements de l'appareil et d'utilisation, des renseignements de géolocalisation précise (si vous avez activé cette fonctionnalité), des fournisseurs de services ainsi que les types d'appareils mobiles et de systèmes d'exploitation accédant à l'application.
  *  ** _Renseignements obtenus d'autres sources_** _:_ Nous pourrions recevoir des renseignements sur vous à partir d'autres sources, par exemple, par l'entremise de fournisseurs tiers, de sources de services et commerciales (tels que les agrégateurs de données et les bases de données publiques). Nous pouvons également recueillir des renseignements que vous publiez publiquement sur nos pages de médias sociaux, tels que nos pages Facebook®, Instagram® et Twitter®. De plus, nous pouvons combiner les renseignements que vous nous fournissez avec d'autres renseignements provenant de sources Beachbody, de communications et de transactions. Lorsque cela est permis par la loi, nous combinons ces renseignements provenant d'autres sources, y compris des sites Web de médias sociaux, avec des renseignements que vous nous fournissez ainsi que des renseignements à votre sujet que nous recueillons automatiquement.

  *  ** _Exemples de renseignements obtenus d'autres sources :_** Ceci inclut, sans s'y limiter, les renseignements que vous fournissez à nos fournisseurs ; le numéro et les dates d'expiration de cartes de crédit mis à jour de votre banque ou de société de cartes de crédit que nous utilisons pour garder nos dossiers à jour et mieux vous servir ; des renseignements à jour de livraison et d'adresse de nos transporteurs ou d'autres tiers que nous utilisons pour garder nos dossiers à jour, traiter les commandes, livrer votre prochain achat, et mieux vous servir ; des renseignements sur les comptes que nous utilisons pour valider l'accès à vos comptes avec nous ; des données transactionnelles provenant d'achat auprès de tiers ; des données démographiques et de profil ; des messages de médias sociaux, tels que sur vos goûts, intérêts, commentaires, préférences, photos, suggestions, opinions et plaintes ; des renseignements que nous pouvons recevoir de votre Coach Team Beachbody (le cas échéant) ; des renseignements que vous fournissez lors de nos campagnes par courriel et de message texte ; des renseignements sur les produits ou services achetés auprès d'autres sociétés. 

**À quelles fins Beachbody utilise-t-elle les renseignements qu'elle recueille  ? **

Beachbody peut utiliser les renseignements fournis ci-dessus de diverses manières, y compris, sans s'y limiter : 

  * Traiter et exécuter vos demandes ou commandes pour tout service de Beachbody, et vérifier votre identité et un emplacement pour permettre l'accès à vos comptes (tels que votre compte Team Beachbody ou Beachbody sur demande) ; 

  * Communiquer avec vous au sujet de vos commandes ou toute question que vous nous avez soumises ; 
  * Informer sur les nouveaux produits, biens ou services, y compris si vous avez commencé une transaction avec nous et fourni vos renseignements, mais que vous n'avez pas terminé votre commande ;
  * Gérer vos comptes, ou communiquer avec vous au sujet de vos comptes ;
  * Résoudre un problème ou répondre à une question concernant votre utilisation de tout service de Beachbody, ou pour en savoir davantage ou vérifier les renseignements relatifs à une transaction ;
  * Vous aider avec vos objectifs de santé et de bien-être, comme vous fournir des conseils et des commentaires sur vos objectifs et vous connecter avec des personnes qui partagent vos intérêts ; 
  * Améliorer les services de Beachbody et la publicité ou le matériel connexe ;
  * Améliorer et personnaliser votre expérience de Beachbody sur tout service de Beachbody et contrôler la fréquence des publicités sur votre appareil ; 
  * Cibler la publicité ou des promotions qui pourraient vous intéresser, tels que les courriels, le publipostage, les bannières publicitaires, des annonces instantanées (annonces qui apparaissent lorsque vous vous connectez ou quittez vos comptes en ligne) ou des promotions en fonction de votre profil démographique, intérêts ou emplacement ; 
  * Vous envoyer des courriels et autres communications au sujet de Beachbody ou de l'un des produits ou services de nos partenaires d'affaires que nous pensons que vous pourriez trouver utiles, ou pour voir si vous êtes intéressé à participer à des sondages, études de marché ou autres demandes de renseignements ; 
  * Administrer des concours, des promotions, des événements, des sondages ou autres éléments ; 
  * Améliorer, personnaliser et optimiser votre navigation sur le site et les expériences d'applications mobiles en examinant les parties de notre site Web que vous visitez ou quel aspect de nos applications mobiles, vous trouverez les plus utiles et améliorer les produits et services actuels ou en développer de nouveaux ;
  * Réaliser, améliorer et maintenir nos services de Beachbody, y compris pour l'analyse des données, tels que le comportement et les tendances d'utilisation et diagnostiquer les problèmes avec notre serveur et administrer nos sites Web ;
  * Nous aider à prendre les précautions de sécurité reliées aux données et participer à la prévention, la détection et le règlement de la fraude ;
  * Réaliser d'autres mesures qui vous sont divulguées et auxquelles vous consentez ; 
  * Réaliser des analyses statistiques et de la recherche, et à des fins démographiques de profilage ; ou
  * Se conformer aux lois, directives, règles, ordonnances et règlements internationaux, fédéraux, de l'État, provinciaux/territoriaux et locaux, des enquêtes civiles, criminelles ou réglementaires ; ou d'autres exigences légales, telles que les ordonnances judiciaires.

 _Données HealthKit de Apple :_ Beachbody n'utilisera ni ne partagera de données reliées à la santé recueillies par le biais de HealthKit de Apple à des fins de marketing.

 **À propos des témoins, des pixels invisibles et des outils de suivi de tiers**

  *  ** _Témoins_** _:_ Comme presque toutes les entreprises, Beachbody et autres utilisent une technologie communément appelée un « témoin ». Il s'agit d'un fichier de données de petite taille que notre serveur place sur votre ordinateur ou appareil mobile pour reconnaître votre appareil et fournir des fonctionnalités et des publicités personnalisées. Les témoins sont largement utilisés par les propriétaires de sites Web afin de faire fonctionner leur sites Web ou de les faire fonctionner plus efficacement, ainsi que de fournir des rapports d'information. Grâce à des témoins, nous sommes en mesure de recueillir des renseignements que nous utilisons pour améliorer nos sites Web et des applications mobiles, améliorer votre expérience et personnaliser vos expériences et des publicités. Par exemple, par le biais des témoins, nous pouvons tenir le compte des visites de retour à notre site Web ou aux sites Web de nos annonceurs ou partenaires, recueillir et communiquer des renseignements statistiques globales, authentifier vos renseignements de connexion et gérer plusieurs instances de nos sites en un seul navigateur. Nous pouvons également recueillir d'autres données par le biais de témoins, tels que la page ou le site Web qui vous a référé à nous, la date et l'heure de votre visite et votre adresse IP actuelle. Les témoins que nous plaçons sur votre disque dur sont connus comme des « témoins de première partie » et tous les témoins placés par des tiers sont appelés des « témoins tiers ». Les témoins tiers permettent des éléments ou des fonctionnalités de tiers à exécuter sur ou via le site Web (par exemple, la publicité, le contenu interactif et des analyses). Les parties qui définissent ces témoins tiers peuvent reconnaître votre ordinateur lorsqu'il visite le site Web en question et aussi lorsqu'il visite certains autres sites. 

  * **_Désactivation des témoins  :_** ****La plupart des principaux navigateurs Web fournissent aux utilisateurs la possibilité d'accepter ou de refuser les témoins. Refuser l'utilisation des témoins pour fournir de la publicité ciblée repose sur l'information contenue dans les témoins uniques placés sur votre navigateur par nos partenaires ; donc si vous supprimez les témoins, utilisez un autre appareil ou changer de navigateur, vous devrez peut-être refuser l'activation de témoins de nouveau. Veuillez prendre note que si vous utilisez des paramètres de votre navigateur pour bloquer tous les témoins, vous pouvez ne pas être en mesure d'accéder à certaines parties de nos sites ou d'autres sites. L'option «  Aide » sur la plupart des navigateurs vous indique comment empêcher votre navigateur d'accepter de nouveaux témoins, comment le navigateur vous avertit lorsque vous recevez un nouveau témoin ou comment désactiver les témoins. De plus, vous pouvez désactiver ou supprimer des données similaires utilisées par des modules complémentaires de navigateur tels que les témoins instantanés en changeant les paramètres du module complémentaire ou en visitant le site de son fabricant. Puisque les témoins vous permettent de profiter de certains de nos fonctionnalités essentielles, nous vous recommandons de les laisser activés. Par exemple, si vous bloquez ou rejeter autrement nos témoins, vous pouvez ne pas être en mesure d'utiliser certaines fonctionnalités sur nos sites Web, tels que l'ajout d'articles à votre panier, passer à la caisse ou utiliser les services qui vous obligent à vous connecter.

  *  ** _Pixels invisibles :_**   Nous recueillons également des renseignements par l'entremise de « pixels invisibles » sur notre site Web et dans les courriels que nous vous envoyons. Ces pixels peuvent être placés par nous ou par l'un de nos partenaires tiers. Les « pixels invisibles », aussi connus sous le nom de « balises Web » sont de tout petits fichiers graphiques ou extraits de code, invisibles à l'œil nu, contenus dans des courriels et des pages Web HTML. Lorsqu'un tel message est consulté sur un serveur de messagerie prenant en charge le langage HTML, l'ordinateur ou l'appareil du destinataire communique avec notre serveur pour récupérer le fichier de pixel invisible, nous permettant ainsi d'enregistrer et de stocker, en plus de l'adresse de courriel du destinataire, la date et l'heure où le courriel a été lu, si le client de messagerie du destinataire peut recevoir (ou non) des courriels en HTML, ainsi que d'autres renseignements standard de connexion. Le pixel invisible peut aussi voir et lire les témoins. Beachbody pourrait se servir des pixels invisibles afin de mesurer et de mieux comprendre l'achalandage, d'améliorer la performance du site, d'analyser les habitudes des visiteurs pour rehausser l'expérience utilisateur et de faire le suivi des réponses aux campagnes promotionnelles et de marketing, entre autres. Vous pouvez désactiver la fonction des pixels invisibles en modifiant les options de votre client de messagerie de sorte à empêcher le téléchargement automatique d'images, en modifiant les paramètres de votre navigateur pour qu'il ignore les images et désactive Java script. Il existe aussi des logiciels commerciaux qui ignorent les pixels invisibles et la plupart des publicités.
  *  ** _Publicité comportementale sur les sites Web de tiers :_** Nous travaillons également avec des tiers qui utilisent des technologies de suivi sur nos sites Web et d'autres sites Web afin de publier et de faire le suivi des publicités personnalisées en notre nom et au nom des autres annonceurs sur Internet. Ces partenaires tiers peuvent placer ou reconnaître un témoin unique sur votre disque dur. Ils peuvent aider Beachbody à placer des témoins de première partie en provenance de nos serveurs ou les témoins tiers à partir de leurs propres serveurs ou d'autres serveurs tiers. Beachbody ainsi que nos annonceurs et partenaires tiers de publicité peuvent utiliser des témoins afin de collecter des renseignements sur vous, ce qui peut comprendre le nombre de fois que vous avez vu une annonce ou si vous avez interagi avec une annonce. Nous et nos partenaires pouvons également utiliser des témoins pour vous fournir de la publicité basée sur les intérêts ou les comportements. L'utilisation de témoins tiers n'est pas couverte par cette politique de confidentialité puisque ces tiers sont soumis à leurs propres politiques de confidentialité. Pour plus de renseignements au sujet de cette pratique et pour comprendre vos options pour plusieurs de nos partenaires de publicité, veuillez visiter _[http://www.youradchoices.com](http://www.youradchoices.com/)_ (É.-U.), _[http://www.youradchoices.ca](http://www.youradchoices.ca/)_ (Canada) ou Network Advertising Initiative à _[www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/)_. Si vous choisissez de refuser de la publicité comportementale utilisant ces témoins, vous aurez toujours des publicités sur Internet, mais elles ne seront peut-être pas adaptées à vos intérêts. La plupart des principaux navigateurs Web fournissent aux utilisateurs la possibilité d'accepter ou de refuser les témoins tiers. Le refuser repose sur l'information dans les témoins uniques placés sur votre navigateur par nos partenaires, donc si vous supprimez les témoins, utilisez un autre appareil ou changez de navigateur, vous devrez peut-être refuser l'activation de témoins de nouveau. 
  * **_Signaux Pas de suivi  :_** Certains navigateurs Web offrent un signal « Pas de suivi » qui est un champ d'en-tête HTTP indiquant vos préférences concernant le suivi ou le suivi à travers sites de différents sites consultés par l'utilisateur. Comme beaucoup d'autres sites et services en ligne, nous ne modifions actuellement pas nos pratiques lorsque nous recevons des signaux Pas de suivi ou d'autres mécanismes qui offrent aux consommateurs la possibilité d'exercer un choix en ce qui concerne la collecte de renseignements personnels sur les activités en ligne d'un consommateur individuel au fil du temps et à travers des sites tiers ou services en ligne car il n'y a pas de consensus parmi les participants de l'industrie quant à ce que « Pas de suivi » signifie dans ce contexte. Pour en savoir plus sur « Pas de suivi », vous pouvez visiter _<http://www.allaboutdnt.com/>__._

 **Est-ce que Beachbody partage les renseignements et les données qu'elle reçoit ?**

La confiance que nos clients ont en nous pour protéger leurs renseignements personnels nous tient à cœur. Nous partageons des renseignements personnels que nous recueillons avec votre consentement et tel que décrit ci-dessous : 

  * **_Les fournisseurs de services tiers :_** Nous avons recours à des entreprises tierces et à des particuliers pour réaliser des fonctions commerciales en notre nom pour mieux vous servir. Par exemple, nous utilisons des tiers pour nous aider à rendre nos produits et services disponibles à vous, traiter les commandes que vous avez placées, traiter les paiements par carte de crédit, offrir le service à la clientèle, expédier du courrier, livrer votre colis, mener des études de marché, des analyses de renseignements, gérer les promotions et communiquer avec vous dans le cadre de divers services de Beachbody. Dans ces cas, nous pouvons avoir besoin de fournir vos renseignements à ces tiers à de telles fins. 

  * **_Attribution d'un Coach Team Beachbody et (ou) d'un instructeur principal  :_** ** ** Afin de maximiser les avantages de nos produits et services, nous attribuons un Coach Team Beachbody indépendant (un «  **Coach**  ») à tous les clients qui acceptent d'être membre du Team Beachbody Club ou qui consentent à être contactés par un Coach. Le Coach qu'on vous aura attitré est là pour vous aider à comprendre et à utiliser les produits que vous commandez et pour vous donner la motivation dont vous avez besoin pour atteindre vos objectifs de mise en forme. Pour faciliter le contact mutuel, votre Coach attitré aura accès à certains renseignements que vous nous aurez fournis lors de votre achat, par exemple vos nom, adresse, numéro de téléphone, adresse de courriel et les noms des produits que vous avez achetés. Votre Coach peut vous contacter pour offrir un soutien et fournir des documents d'information générales et de marketing. Veuille prendre note que Beachbody ne fournira jamais à votre Coach attitré les renseignements de votre carte de crédit ou de débit ou, si vous l'avez fourni, votre numéro de sécurité sociale/numéro d'assurance sociale. Si vous vous êtes joint à Beachbody LIVE !, nous pouvons fournir certains renseignements de base sur l'instructeur principal qui vous est attitré pendant votre formation, tels que vos nom, adresse de courriel et numéro de téléphone. 
  * **_Entreprises associées ; offres de tiers :_** Occasionnellement, Beachbody s'associe à des tiers pour en savoir plus sur nos clients afin que nous puissions mieux vous servir ou offrir des produits ou de services que nous croyons pouvoir vous être utiles (« **entreprise associée** »). Dans ce cas, nous pouvons divulguer à une entreprise associée certains renseignements, tels que vos nom, courriel, adresse de facturation ou d'expédition, les produits achetés et le prix. Si vous demandez des informations à partir d'une entreprise associée, nous pouvons divulguer des renseignements supplémentaires tels que vos adresse de courriel, numéro de téléphone et d'autres informations de contact, de sorte que l'entreprise associée puisse vous fournir l'information demandée. Si vous avez acheté un produit ou un service à partir d'une entreprise associée, nous divulguerons également vos renseignements de carte de crédit afin de pouvoir traiter votre achat. Nous pouvons divulguer des renseignements agrégés, anonymisés à des entreprises associées : (i) de sorte que les entreprises associées puissent vous offrir des publicités adaptées à vos intérêts ; (ii) pour l'analyse statistique, de la recherche et à des fins de profilage démographiques ; et (iii) pour soutenir notre entreprise et améliorer notre mission d'aider nos clients à atteindre leurs objectifs de santé et de bien-être.
  *  ** _Protection des Beachbody et autres  :_** Nous pouvons partager vos renseignements, y compris des renseignements personnels identifiables, afin de: (i) protéger ou défendre les droits ou la propriété de Beachbody, ou les droits de nos clients, nos Coachs, partenaires d'affaires, employés, agents et sous-traitants ; (ii) protéger la sécurité de nos clients, des Coachs ou des membres du public, y compris agir en cas d'urgence ; (iii) détecter et protéger contre la fraude et l'usurpation d'identité ou de procéder à la gestion des risques ; (iv) se conformer aux lois, procédures judiciaires ou des demandes légales d'un organisme gouvernemental ou réglementaire ; ou (v) faire respecter ou appliquer les modalités ou autres accords de notre site.
  *  ** _Divulgation de données anonymisées  :_** Nous pourrions aussi révéler des renseignements non signalétiques relatifs aux transactions à des tiers aux fins de comptabilité et de tenue de dossiers. Nous pouvons également divulguer, les données utilisateur agrégées et anonymisées ou des renseignements non personnels à des partenaires commerciaux, des annonceurs et autres.

 **À propos des services de tiers et d'annonceurs**

À divers moments et pages sur nos sites Web ou applications mobiles, vous pourriez être en mesure d'accéder ou d'utiliser les services offerts par ou en conjonction avec des tiers. Cela comprend les services en relation avec des « médias sociaux » de tiers et d'autres sites qui permettrait le transfert de renseignements personnels à ces tiers (par exemple, Facebook Connect), Coachs et autres. 

Ces tiers ont des pratiques de collecte de données et de confidentialité distinctes et indépendantes de la nôtre, donc veuillez prendre connaissance de leurs politiques de confidentialité pour comprendre vos droits. Pour cette raison, Beachbody ne peut pas être tenue responsable de leurs politiques ou de leurs activités. Veuillez communiquer directement avec ces tiers si vous avez des questions au sujet de leurs pratiques de confidentialité. 

**À quel point les renseignements à mon sujet sont-ils sécurisés ?**

Beachbody a mis en place et utilise des mesures de sécurité raisonnables conçues pour aider à prévenir la perte et l'accès non autorisé à vos renseignements. Malgré ces efforts, aucune mesure de sécurité n'est parfaite ou impénétrable, et aucune méthode de transmission de données ne peut être garantie contre l'interception ou être absolument sure. En conséquence, bien que nous nous efforçons de protéger vos renseignements personnels, nous ne pouvons pas assurer ou garantir la sécurité des informations que vous nous transmettez ou de nos services en ligne. Si vous soupçonnez qu'un site Web ou qu'une application mobile prétend être celui de Beachbody (également connu sous le nom « mystification »), n'entrez pas de renseignements personnels et veuillez nous en aviser par courriel à _[CyberSecurity@Beachbody.com](mailto:CyberSecurity@Beachbody.com)_. Les renseignements personnels peuvent être accessibles par des personnes au sein de notre organisation, ou nos fournisseurs de services tiers, qui ont besoin d'un tel accès pour réaliser les fins indiquées ci-dessus ou toutes autres fins pouvant être autorisées ou requises par la loi applicable. Les renseignements personnels que nous recueillons sont traités aux États-Unis. 

**Qu'arrivera-t-il à mes renseignements si Beachbody est vendue à une autre société ou fusionne avec une autre société  ?**

Alors que nous continuons à développer et à accroître notre entreprise ou dans le cas improbable d'une faillite, nous pourrions vendre un ou plusieurs de nos actifs, filiales ou unités d'affaires. Dans de telles transactions, les renseignements au sujet des clients est généralement l'un des actifs transférés. 

**Utilisateurs à l'extérieur des É.-U. ; transfert de renseignements personnels**

Comme la plupart des sites Web et des entreprises, les sites Web de Beachbody peuvent être consultés par un public international. En visitant nos sites Web, en utilisant nos applications, et (ou) en nous fournissant des données, vous acceptez que nous puissions recueillir, traiter, utiliser et enregistrer vos renseignements personnels, tel que discuté ici, en dehors de la juridiction de votre lieu de résidence (comme aux États-Unis ou au Canada). Nos sociétés associées et les fournisseurs de services tiers peuvent aussi être situés en dehors de votre instance administrative. En conséquence, ces renseignements peuvent être soumis à des demandes d'accès des gouvernements, des tribunaux ou organismes d'application de la loi dans ces juridictions conformément aux lois de ces juridictions. Veuillez prendre note que la loi des É.-U. et celle d'autres pays où vos renseignements peuvent être enregistrés et traités peuvent offrir niveaux de protection pour vos renseignements différents de ceux de votre pays d'origine. Nous prendrons toutes les mesures raisonnables pour veiller à ce que ces renseignements personnels soient traités en toute sécurité et conformément à la présente politique de confidentialité.

 **Comment puis-je accéder ou actualiser mes renseignements  ?**

Nous voulons être sûrs que vos renseignements personnels demeurent exacts et complets, et pour cette raison, nous vous demandons de nous informer en cas de tout changement à vos renseignements. Si vous avez fourni vos renseignements _directement à Beachbody_ , vous pouvez accéder ou mettre à jour certains renseignements personnels en communiquant avec notre service à la clientèle au (800) 470-7870 ou en vous connectant à votre compte Team Beachbody si vous avez créé un. Lors de l'appel au service à la clientèle, veuillez avoir votre adresse de courriel et des informations de commande. Nous prendrons toutes les mesures commercialement raisonnables pour répondre à votre demande d'accès ou mettre vos renseignements à jour. Veuillez prendre note que certains peuvent faire l'objet de frais. 

**Vos choix reliés à la confidentialité  : Refus **

  * **_Marketing :_** Nous vous proposons différentes façons de refuser de recevoir certaines de nos communications. Si vous souhaitez refuser de recevoir des communications de marketing par courriel de notre part, vous pouvez cliquer sur le lien « Se désabonner » au bas des courriels de marketing de Beachbody que nous envoyons et suivre les instructions simples de refus ou vous pouvez cliquer sur les liens « Préférences » pour mettre à jour vos paramètres de courriel. Si vous souhaitez refuser de recevoir des appels téléphoniques de marketing, vous pouvez informer l'agent avec qui vous parlez que vous souhaitez être placé sur la liste « Ne pas téléphoner » de Beachbody. Si vous souhaitez refuser de recevoir toute campagne par messagerie texte de Beachbody, veuillez suivre les instructions fournies lorsque vous acceptez la campagne ; généralement, répondre « ARRÊT » à votre code court spécifique vous retire de la campagne pour laquelle vous vous êtes inscrit.

  *  ** _Publicité en ligne :_** Pour apprendre quelques-unes des façons par lesquelles vous pouvez refuser de la publicité ciblée en ligne, consultez la section ci-dessus intitulée « À propose des témoins, des pixels invisibles et des outils de suivi de tiers » pour obtenir plus de renseignements. 

**Modifications à cette politique de confidentialité**

Beachbody peut modifier à tout moment cette politique de confidentialité et ces modifications entrent en vigueur dès leur publication sur nos sites Web. La poursuite de notre relation d'affaires avec nous ou de votre utilisation de nos sites Web faisant suite à la publication de ces modifications constitue votre acceptation des modifications, tant en ce qui concerne les renseignements que nous avons déjà recueillis que ceux que nous recueillerons ultérieurement. 

**Avis aux résidents de la Californie - Vos droits de la protection des renseignements personnels de la Californie (tel que prévu à l'article 1798.83 du California Civil Code).**

Un résident de la Californie qui a fourni des données à caractère personnel, au sens de l'article 1798.83 du California Civil Code, à une entreprise avec laquelle il a établi une relation d'affaires à des fins personnelles, de la famille ou du ménage (un «  **client de la Californie**  ») peut s'informer pour vérifier si l'entreprise a communiqué des renseignements personnels à des tiers à des fins de marketing direct des tiers. En général, si l'entreprise a fait une telle divulgation de données à caractère personnel, à la réception d'une demande d'un client de la Californie, l'entreprise est tenue de fournir une liste de tous les tiers auxquels les données personnelles ont été divulguées dans l'année civile précédente, ainsi qu'une liste des catégories de données personnelles qui ont été divulguées. Les clients de la Californie peuvent demander de plus amples renseignements sur notre conformité à cette loi par courriel à _[Privacy@Beachbody.com](mailto:Privacy@beachbody.com)_. Veuillez prendre note que nous sommes tenus de répondre à une demande par client de la Californie chaque année et que nous ne sommes pas tenus de répondre aux demandes formulées par d'autres moyens que par le biais de cette adresse de courriel.

 **Communiquer avec Beachbody**

N'hésitez pas à nous faire part de vos commentaires, vos préoccupations ou vos questions : 

Chief Legal Officer

Beachbody, LLC – Attn: Legal Department

3301 Exposition Blvd.

Santa Monica, CA 90404 USA

ou envoyez-nous un courriel : _[Privacy@Beachbody.com](mailto:Privacy@beachbody.com)_

## BEACHBODY UK LTD. PRIVACY NOTICE

 **For residents outside the U.S. and Canada**

 _Effective Date_ : May 24, 2018

 **Introduction**

Beachbody UK Ltd., together with our parent company, affiliates, and subsidiaries (collectively, “ **Beachbody** ”, “ **us** ”, “ **we** ” or “ **our** ”) know that you care about how your information is collected, used, protected and shared, and we appreciate the trust you place in us that we will do so carefully and sensibly. We provide you with this Privacy Notice because we want you to know how we may collect, use, protect and share information about you, and the choices and privacy rights that are available to you. 

To review our **Cookie Notice** , please scroll down to the bottom of this Privacy Notice or click _here_.

Please don’t hesitate to contact us at any time if you have any questions regarding the contents in this Privacy Notice by visiting the “ _Contacting Beachbody_” section below. 

**Table of Contents for Privacy Notice**

 _When Does this Privacy Notice Apply?_

 _What Information Does Beachbody Collect From You?_

 _How Does Beachbody Use the Information It Collects?_

 _Who Does Beachbody Share your Information with?_

 _What About Cookies, Pixel Tags and Third Party Tracking Tools?_

 _What About Third-Party Resellers’ and Advertisers’ Services?_

 _How Secure is the Information Beachbody Has About Me?_

_What About Information Pertaining to Children?_

 _Transfers of Personal Information_

 _How Can I Update My Information?_

 _What are your Other Privacy Choices?_

 _How Can you Exercise your Other Privacy Rights?_

 _How Long do we Retain your Information?_

 _Legal Basis for Processing Personal Information_

 _Changes to This Privacy Notice_

 _Contacting Beachbody_

 **Table of Contents for Cookie Notice**

 **BEACHBODY UK LTD. COOKIE NOTICE**

 _What Are Cookies?_

 _Why Do We Use Cookies?_

 _What About Other Tracking Technologies, Like Web Beacons?_

 _Do You Use Flash cookies or Local Shared Objects?_

 _Do You Serve Targeted Advertising?_

 _How Can I Control Cookies?_

 _How Often Will You Update This Cookie Statement?_

 _Where Can I Get Further Information?_

 **When Does this Privacy Notice Apply?**

This Privacy Notice applies whenever we collect personal information (including any "sensitive" or "special categories" of personal information, such as health information) from or about you in connection with any and all of the goods and services that we provide, including our:

  * Websites, such as Beachbody.com, TeamBeachbody.com and BeachbodyOnDemand.com; 
  * Mobile applications, such as the Beachbody On Demand app, My Challenge Tracker app and Nutrition app;
  * Videos and other content delivered to you via DVDs or our streaming services;
  * Other products, equipment, surveys, promotions, software, technology, etc.; or 
  * Telesales and/or Customer Service Departments. 

(collectively, “ **Beachbody Services** ”). 

**What Information Does Beachbody Collect From You?**

The information we receive from you allows us to provide Beachbody Services to you, as well as to personalize your experience and continually improve our business. Here are the general types of personal information we gather: 

**_Information You Give to Us_** : We receive, store and process personal information that you provide to us through the Beachbody Services – for example, when you sign up for and use Beachbody On Demand, consult with our Customer Service department, enter information on our websites, purchase goods and services from us, participate in contests or other promotions, take surveys, and send us an email or communicate with us in any way. 

Where we ask you to provide your personal information, it should be apparent whether it is required or not. Note that, in some cases, you may choose to not provide us with your personal information however, this may limit our ability to provide you with the Beachbody Services. Learn more by reviewing the table below. 

Examples of when you provide your personal information to Beachbody:| Personal Information Types (Examples)  
---|---  
  
When you **enquire about, purchase, activate or use the Beachbody Services** (on any device); or 

When you **communicate with us** or other users via our website, message boards, social media accounts, phone, e-mail, texts, surveys, or participate in promotions, surveys or in any other way

| 

For these purposes, we will collect information such as:

  * your name; 
  * shipping, billing, and/or business addresses; 
  * location information (if you provide or consent to give us this information) 
  * phone number; 
  * e-mail address; 
  * username and password information;
  * credit or other payment card information; 
  * gender; 
  * date of birth; and 
  * survey response data

To **track your workout activity** when you use the Beachbody Services or when you participate in a test group or activity with Beachbody:

| 

For these purposes, we will collect information you provide such as the following, to help you achieve your health and wellness goals: 

  * physical information (e.g., weight, waist, hip and bicep measurements, etc.); 
  * food and nutritional information (e.g., types of food and beverages consumed, and any related caloric, fat, fiber, cholesterol and other information); 
  * metabolic information (e.g., caloric and fat burn through exercise, and other related information); 
  * fitness and activity information (e.g., the types and number of workouts you may be using, workout and activity tracking, hours exercised, etc.); and 
  * general feedback (e.g., content you post on message boards, or information you submit about our products, goods or services).

 _Apple HealthKit Data_ : To help track your workout activity (such as displaying your heart rate and estimating your calorie burn) when using certain Beachbody Services, Beachbody may send and receive data to and from Apple’s Healthkit Application if you have enabled this feature. Beachbody will not use or share health data collected through Apple HealthKit for marketing purposes. We will use this data to enhance your overall experience using Beachbody Services, such as to display your heart rate and estimate your calorie burn while performing exercises with Beachbody programs.

 **Note:** Some of this information is viewed by some countries as "sensitive" or "special categories of data". If applicable, we will not collect and use such personal information about you (including, for example, racial or ethnic origin, physical or mental health or condition, or sexual life) without your consent or as otherwise permitted by applicable law.

When you **sign up as a Team Beachbody Coach**

| 

For these purposes, we will collect information such as:

  * your name; 
  * shipping, billing, and/or business addresses; 
  * location information (if you provide or consent to give us this information) 
  * phone number; 
  * e-mail address; 
  * username and password information;
  * credit or other payment card information; 
  * gender; 
  * date of birth; 
  * social security/social insurance or other similar identification number for tax purposes;
  * bank account information in order to remit any commission payments you may have earned.

When you apply to **join our Affiliate Programme**

| 

For this purposes, we will collect information about your affiliate business, such as:

  * your (or your organization's) name;
  * e-mail address;
  * street address;
  * telephone number; 
  * tax identification number; and
  * information about your website and users (e.g., the URL, the number of unique users and page views, the demographics of your user base, etc.)

 ** _Information We Automatically Receive_** : When you use or interact with certain Beachbody Services, we may automatically receive and store certain technical information about your device and usage of the Beachbody Services. Like many other websites and online services, we use “cookies” and other similar tracking technologies to collect some of this information to help enhance your experience on the Beachbody Services. For more information about our use of "cookies" and other tracking technologies, please see our Cookie Notice by clicking here. Learn more about the information we automatically receive by reviewing the table below:

Examples of when your information is automatically received by Beachbody:| Personal Information Types (Examples)  
---|---  
  
When you **visit our websites, download, install or use our applications** through mobile or other devices or otherwise **interact with Beachbody Services** (on any device);

| 

For these purposes, we will collect information about you or your device such as:

  * Internet protocol (IP) address (the number used to identify your computer or modem to the Internet, which can potentially identify your location and Internet Service Provider);
  * Browser type;
  * Device type;
  * Time zone setting;
  * Operating system; 
  * Information about your activities on our websites, including the Uniform Resource Locator (URL) from which you came to our websites and the URLs that you visited on our websites;
  * Cookie number; 
  * Products you viewed or searched for; 
  * The phone number you used to call us; and
  * Pixel tag data as described below.

To ensure the **operation of the Beachbody Services** and **protect you against fraud, security** and for **diagnostic purposes**.

| 

During some visits to our websites, we may use software tools such as JavaScript to measure and collect session information, including: 

  * page response times;
  * download errors, length of visits to certain pages;
  * page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs);
  * methods used to browse away from the page; 
  * other technical information; and 
  * the information listed in the column directly above.

When you have **consented to allowing our applications to access information on your device**

| 

When you first launch any of our applications that collect location information or access your camera, microphone, or other device services or hardware, you will be asked to consent before the application does so. If you initially consent, you can subsequently stop the collection or access at any time by changing the preferences on your mobile device. If you do so, our mobile applications, or certain features within the application, may no longer function. **_Please review your device settings for more information._**  

 ** _Information We Obtain From Other Sources_** : We may receive information about you from other sources, including from third party vendors, services and commercially available sources (such as data aggregators and public databases) so that we can provide the best personalized services to you. 

We may also collect information that you publicly post on our social media pages, such as our Facebook®, Instagram®, and Twitter® pages. In addition, we may combine information you give us with other information from Beachbody sources, communications and transactions. Where permitted by law, we combine this information received from other sources, including from social media websites, with information you give us and information that we collect automatically about you. Learn more by reviewing the table below.

Examples of when your information is obtained from third parties by Beachbody:| Personal Information Types (Examples)  
---|---  
  
When you **talk about us publically, including on social media** , and we want to **understand you better**

| 

  * Your name;
  * Social media handle; 
  * Information included within your statements about us;
  * Demographic and profile data;
  * Social media posts, including your likes;
  * Interests;
  * Feedback; 
  * Preferences;
  * Pictures;
  * Comments, suggestions, opinions, and complaints; and
  * Information about products or services purchased from other companies

When your **payment card details, address** or **other information is updated** which we use to keep your records current and service you better

| 

  * Updated credit card number and expiration dates
  * Your delivery details

When we need to **validate access to your account**

| 

  * Account information

When your **Team Beachbody Coach shares personal information** with us

| 

  * Account information;
  * Information relating to contest entries; and
  * Coach activity

 **How Does Beachbody Use the Information It Collects?**

Beachbody uses your personal information where we have a legitimate business reason to do so, where it is necessary for the performance of a contract with you, required by law, or with your consent. 

In addition to what is listed in the tables above, such reasons include: 

  * **Processing your orders for and delivering the Beachbody Services.** We need your personal information so that we can process and fulfill your orders for any Beachbody Services. In processing your order, we may need you to verify your identity and/or location to allow access to your accounts (such as your Team Beachbody or Beachbody On Demand account); 
  * **Communicating with you about your orders,** any inquiries you may have submitted to us or other customer service issues;
  *  **Telling you about our products, goods or services** , including where you started a transaction with us and provided your information, but did not finalize your order;
  *  **Servicing and managing your accounts,** or contacting you about your accounts;
  *  **Troubleshooting,** addressing a problem or issue affecting your use of any Beachbody Services, or to inquire about or verify information concerning a transaction;
  *  **Process any event or other similar registrations** for our events if you signed up; 
  * **Assisting you with your health and wellness goals** , such as providing you with advice and feedback on your goals, and connecting you with individuals who share your interests (provided we inform you or you give us your consent to make the connection); 
  * **Enhancing and personalizing your Beachbody experience** on any Beachbody Services, and controlling the frequency of advertisements to your device; 
  * **Targeting advertising or promotions that may be of interest to you** , such as e-mails, direct mail, banner ads, splash ads (ads that appear as you sign in or out of your online accounts) or promotions based on your demographic profile, interests, or location; 
  * **Feature you in advertisements or promotions,** but only if you have signed documentation giving us permission to do so; 
  * **Improving any Beachbody Services,** such as the look and feel of our apps or websites, and related advertising or materials;
  * Sending you **offers about Beachbody's or any of our business partners' products or services** that we think you may find useful (via email and other electronic means and, where necessary, with your consent), in accordance with your marketing preferences;
  *  **Administering contests, promotions, events, market research, surveys** or other features; 
  * **Improve, personalize, and optimize your experience with Beachbody Services** by examining which parts of our website you visit or which aspect of our mobile applications you find most useful, to improve existing or develop new Beachbody Services **;**
  *  **Operating and maintaining our Beachbody Services** , including for data analysis, such as user behavior and trends, and diagnose problems with our server and administer our websites;
  * Assisting us in taking **data security precautions** and to engage in fraud prevention, detection, and remediation;
  * Undertaking **statistical analysis and research** , and for demographic profiling purposes;
  *  **Complying with applicable international, federal, state, provincial and local laws** , directives, rules, regulations, and ordinances; civil, criminal or regulatory investigations; or other legal requirements, such as court orders; and
  *  **Carrying out other purposes which are disclosed to you** and, where necessary, following your consent.

 **Who Does Beachbody Share your Information with?**

We value the trust our customers place in us to safeguard their personal information. We share personal information we collect as described below: 

  * **_Third-Party Service Providers_** : We utilize third party companies and individuals to perform business functions on our behalf to better serve you. For example, we use third parties to help us make our products and services available to you, fulfill orders you may have placed, process credit card payments, provide customer service, payment optimization, seek collections on past due amounts, ship postal mail, deliver your packages, conduct market research or information analysis, manage promotions, and contact you in connection with various Beachbody Services. In these instances, we may need to provide your information to these third parties for such purposes. The categories of such third parties include: order and fulfillment providers; customer service and telesales providers; technology providers; banking, finance and payment processing providers; government agencies or regulators; event management providers (if you signed up for a Beachbody event or similar activity); and marketing providers.
  *  ** _Assignment to a Team Beachbody Coach and/or Master Trainer_** : If the Team Beachbody Coaching opportunity is available in your jurisdiction, we will assign an independent Team Beachbody Coach (a “ **Coach** ”) to all customers who purchase a product from us or who consent to being contacted by a Coach. Your assigned Coach is available to assist you in understanding and using the products you ordered, and give you the motivation you need to help you achieve your fitness goals. To help you both get in contact, your assigned Coach will receive access to certain information you provided during your purchase process, such as your name, address, phone number, e-mail address and the names of the products you purchased. Your Coach may contact you to offer support, and provide general information and marketing materials. Please note that Beachbody will never provide your assigned Coach your credit or debit card information or, if you provided it, your Social Security number/Social Insurance number. If you joined Beachbody LIVE!, we may provide certain basic information to the Master Trainer assigned to train you during your training, such as your name, e-mail address and phone number. 
  * **_Related Companies; Third Party Offers_** : Beachbody occasionally partners with third parties to learn more about our customers so we can service you better or offer products or services that we feel may be useful to you (" **Related Company** "). In such case, we may disclose to a Related Company certain information, such as your name, e-mail, billing or shipping address, products purchased and price. If you request information from a Related Company, we may disclose additional information such as your e-mail address, phone number and other contact information, so the Related Company can provide you with the information you requested. If you purchased a product or service from a Related Company, we will also disclose your credit card information so they can complete your purchase. In other cases, we may disclose aggregated, de-identified information (which _does not_ identify you) to Related Companies: (i) so the Related Companies can provide you with advertisements tailored to your interests; (ii) for statistical analysis, research, and demographic profiling purposes; and (iii) to support our business and improve our mission to help our customers achieve their health and wellness goals.
  *  ** _Protection of Beachbody and Others_** : We may share your information, including personal information, in order to: (i) protect or defend the legal rights or property of Beachbody, or the legal rights of our customers, Coaches, business partners, employees, agents, and contractors; (ii) protect the safety and security of our customers, Coaches or members of the public, including acting in urgent circumstances; (iii) detect and protect against fraud, and identity theft or to conduct risk management; (iv) comply with laws, legal process, or legal requests from any governmental or regulatory body; or (v) to enforce or apply our website Terms and Conditions and/or other agreements. 
  * **_To a buyer or potential buyer of all or part of Beachbody:_** As we continue to develop and grow our business, we might sell one or more of our assets, subsidiaries or business units, or buy a subsidiary or business unit from a third party. In such transactions, customer information is typically one of the transferred business assets, but remains subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Notice (unless the customer consents otherwise). If this should happen, we will provide you with notice of any such transfer by posting to our website or other form of communication. 
  * **_De-identified Data Disclosures_** : We may also disclose non-identifying transaction information (which _does not_ identify you) to third parties for the purpose of accounting and record keeping. We may also disclose aggregated, de-identified information or non-personal information (which _does not_ identify you) with business partners, advertisers, and others.
  *  ** _Other Disclosures_** : Occasionally, we may disclose personal information in other circumstances, but we will only do this if we have explained at the time we collect the information the purpose for which it will be disclosed.

 **What About Cookies, Pixel Tags and Third Party Tracking Tools?**

Like almost every company, Beachbody uses cookies and similar technologies. Please see our Cookie Notice by clicking _here_. 

**What About Third-Party Resellers’ and Advertisers’ Services?**

At various places and pages on our websites or mobile applications, you may be able to access or utilize services offered by or in conjunction with third parties. This includes services in connection with third-party "social media" and other sites that would allow personal information to be transferred to such third parties (for example, Facebook Connect). In addition, certain purchases that you make on our websites or applications may be completed by or through our authorized reseller (“ **Reseller** ”). You will be required to provide your personal information to the Reseller who will charge your payment card or other payment method for any Beachbody products or services you wish to purchase. When this happens, we will notify you of the name of the Reseller and present or direct you to their terms and conditions and privacy notice for your review. 

These third parties (including Resellers, Coaches and others to whom you provide your personal information) have separate data collection and privacy practices independent from ours, so please review their privacy policies to understand your rights. For this reason, Beachbody cannot be responsible for their policies or activities. Please contact those third parties directly if you have questions about their privacy practices. 

**How Secure is the Information Beachbody Has About Me?**

Beachbody has implemented and uses reasonable security measures designed to prevent the loss and unauthorized access of your information. Despite these efforts, no security measures are perfect or impenetrable, and no method of data transmission can be guaranteed against interception or to be absolutely secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or our online services. 

If you suspect an e-mail, website or mobile application is pretending to be that of Beachbody’s (also known as “spoofing”), do not enter any personal information, but please let us know by e-mailing _[CyberSecurity@Beachbody.com](mailto:CyberSecurity@Beachbody.com)_.

 **What About Information Pertaining to Children?**

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 16. If we learn that we have inadvertently obtained personal information on a child under the age of 16, that information will be deleted from our systems. Beachbody encourages parents to go online with their children to help keep them safe. 

**Transfers of Personal Information**

Like most websites and businesses, Beachbody’s websites may be accessed by an international audience. By using any Beachbody Services and/or providing us with any data, you acknowledge we may collect, process, use, and store your personal information as discussed herein, including outside your resident jurisdiction (such as the U.S. and Canada). Our related companies and third party service providers may also be located outside of your jurisdiction. Please note that U.S. law and those of other countries where your information may be stored and processed may offer different levels of protection for your information than your home country. We will take all reasonable steps to ensure that such personal information is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Notice.

Where applicable, we have taken appropriate safeguards to require that your personal information will remain protected in accordance with this Privacy Notice. These include implementing the European Commission’s Standard Contractual Clauses for transfers of personal information between our affiliate and subsidiary companies, which require all such companies to protect personal information they process from the European Economic Area in accordance with European Union data protection law. 

Our Standard Contractual Clauses can be provided by making a request at _[Privacy@Beachbody.com](mailto:Privacy@Beachbody.com)_. We have implemented similar appropriate safeguards with certain third party service providers and partners. Further details can be provided upon request.

 **How Can I Update My Information?**

We want to be sure your personal information is kept accurate and complete, and for this reason we ask that you inform us or our Reseller in the event of any changes to your information. 

  * If you provided your information _directly to Beachbody_ , you may access and update certain personal information by calling our Customer Service at +44 (0)121 620 8111 or logging into your Team Beachbody account if you created one. When calling Customer Service, please have your e-mail address and order information available. You may also make a request to update your information at any time by visiting _<https://faq.beachbody.com/app/gdpr_form>_. 

  * If you purchased any Beachbody Services _through a Reseller and provided your information directly to the Reseller_ , please contact the Reseller to update and manage your personal information. 

  * If you want to update information in connection with your Beachbody On Demand membership, please visit the “My Account” section within your Beachbody On Demand account for more information. 

If you are unable to update your information via one of the methods above, please see “ _How Can you Exercise your Other Privacy Right_ s” below.

 **What are your Other Privacy Choices?**

 ** _Marketing_** : We always offer you various ways to opt-out of receiving certain communications from us, Related Companies or other third parties. If you would like to opt-out of receiving e-mail marketing communications, you may visit our Preference Center which you can access through links at the bottom of e-mails you receive from us or by visiting the My Account tab when you are logged into _[www.TeamBeachbody.com](https://www.teambeachbody.com/)_. If you would like to opt-out of receiving marketing phone calls, you can inform the agent with whom you speak that you would like to be placed on Beachbody’s “Do Not Call” list. If you would like to opt-out of any Beachbody text message campaign, please follow the instructions provided when you opt-in to the campaign; typically, responding “STOP” to your specific short code will opt you out of the campaign for which you signed up. For help or information regarding your Beachbody On Demand membership, please visit the “My Account” section within your Beachbody On Demand account.

 ** _Online Advertising_** : To learn some of the ways that you can opt-out of targeted online advertising, see the section titled “ _How Can I Control Cookies_?" in the Cookie Notice below for more information. 

**How Can you Exercise your Other Privacy Rights?**

Depending on where you reside, you may have the following privacy rights:

  * If you wish to **access, correct, update or request deletion** of your personal information, you can make such a request at any time by visiting _<https://faq.beachbody.com/app/gdpr_form>_. 

  * In addition, if you are a resident of the European Union, you can **object to the processing** of your personal information, ask us to **restrict processing** of your personal information or **request portability** of your personal information. Again, you can make such a request at any time by visiting _<https://faq.beachbody.com/app/gdpr_form>_. 

  * Similarly, if we have collected and process your personal information with your consent, then you can **withdraw your consent** at any time by visiting our Preference Center which you can access through links at the bottom of e-mails you receive from us or by visiting the My Account tab when you are logged into _[www.TeamBeachbody.com](https://www.teambeachbody.com/)_. Withdrawing your consent will not affect the lawfulness of any processing we conducted prior to your withdrawal, nor will it affect processing of your personal information conducted in reliance on lawful processing grounds other than consent.

  * You have the **right to complain to a data protection authority** about our collection and use of your personal information. For more information, please contact your local data protection authority. 

We respond to all requests we receive from individuals wishing to exercise their data protection rights in accordance with applicable data protection laws.

 **How Long do we Retain your Information?**

We retain personal information we collect from you for as long as we: (i) have an ongoing legitimate business need to do so in connection with the purposes set out at “ _How Does Beachbody Use the Information It Collects?_ ” above (for example to process your information whilst you are a customer and afterwards in order to deal with complaints and queries); or (ii) where required by law (for example we are required to keep financial records for a certain period under VAT and accounting rules). 

When we have no ongoing legitimate business need to process your personal information, we will either delete or anonymise it or, if this is not possible (for example, because your personal information has been stored in backup archives), then we will securely store your personal information and isolate it from any further processing until deletion is possible.

 **Legal Basis for Processing Personal Information**

Our legal basis for collecting and using the personal information described above will depend on the personal information concerned and the specific context in which we collect it. However, we will normally collect personal information from you: (i) where we need the personal information to perform a contract with you for the Beachbody Services; (ii) where the processing is in our legitimate interests and not overridden by your rights; (iii) where we have your consent to do so; or (iv) as required by law. In some cases, we may have a legal obligation to collect personal information from you or may otherwise need the personal information to protect your vital interests or those of another person (for example, if you were to get injured in connection with one of our Beachbody Services).

If we collect and use your personal information in reliance on our legitimate interests (or those of any third party), this interest will normally be to operate our platform and communicating with you as necessary to provide our services to you and for our legitimate commercial interest, for instance, when responding to your queries, improving our platform, undertaking marketing, or for the purposes of detecting or preventing illegal activities. We may have other legitimate interests and if appropriate it will be clear to you at the relevant time what those legitimate interests are.

If you have questions about or need further information concerning the legal basis on which we collect and use your personal information, please contact us using the contact details provided under the “ _Contacting Beachbody_” heading below.

 **Changes to This Privacy Notice**

We may update this Privacy Notice from time to time in response to changing legal, technical or business developments. When we update our Privacy Notice, we will take appropriate measures to inform you, consistent with the significance of the changes we make. We will obtain your consent to any material Privacy Notice changes if and where this is required by applicable data protection laws. 

You can see when this Privacy Notice was last updated by checking the “last updated” date displayed at the top of this Privacy Notice. 

**Contacting Beachbody**

The data controller of your personal information is Beachbody UK Ltd.

Please feel free to share any comments or questions with us: 

Beachbody UK Ltd.

Attn: Legal Department

3301 Exposition Blvd.

Santa Monica, CA 90404

or email us: _[Privacy@Beachbody.com](mailto:Privacy@Beachbody.com)_

**BEACHBODY UK LTD. COOKIE NOTICE**

 _Effective Date_ : May 24, 2018

This Cookie Notice explains how Beachbody UK Ltd. (“ **Beachbody** ”, “ **us** ”, “ **we** ” or “ **our** ”) uses cookies and similar technologies to recognise you when you visit our websites or applications on mobile or connected devices. It explains what these technologies are and why we use them, as well as your rights to control our use of them.

 **What Are Cookies?**

Cookies are small data files that are placed on your computer or mobile device when you visit a website. Cookies are widely used by many companies and website owners in order to make their websites work, or to work more efficiently, as well as to provide reporting information. 

Cookies set by Beachbody are called "first party cookies". Cookies set by parties other than Beachbody are called "third party cookies". Third party cookies enable third party features or functionality to be provided on or through the website (e.g., advertising, interactive content and analytics). The parties that set these third party cookies can recognise your computer both when it visits the website in question and also when it visits certain other websites. 

**Why Do We Use Cookies?**

We use first party and third party cookies. Cookies help us manage and report on your interaction with our websites or mobile applications. Through cookies, we are able to collect information that we use to improve our websites and mobile applications, and improve your overall experience on them. For example, through cookies, we can keep count of return visits to our website or our advertisers' or partners' websites, collect and report on aggregate statistical information, authenticate your login credentials, and manage multiple instances of our websites in a single browser. We may also collect other data through cookies, such as the page or website that referred you to us, the date and time you visited us, and your current IP address.

We use both session cookies and persistent cookies. A session cookie expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You may be able to remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your browser's "help" section.

Some cookies are required for technical reasons in order for our websites to operate, and we refer to these as "essential" or "strictly necessary" cookies. Other cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our websites. Third parties serve cookies through our websites for advertising, analytics and other purposes. This is described in more detail below.

Some of the first and third party cookies we commonly serve through our websites and the purposes they perform are described in the table below. Please note this list is not intended to be exhaustive, but is intended to illustrate primary reasons for certain types of cookies set by Beachbody and third parties on our websites and applications. Also, the specific cookies served may vary depending on the specific website you visit. Since we are always making improvements to our websites and applications to better serve you, the list of companies named in the table below may change from time to time. We will take commercially reasonable efforts to update this Cookie Notice as frequently as possible to reflect the most accurate information.

Types of Cookie| Who Serves These Cookies?| How to Potentially Refuse  
---|---|---  
  
 **Essential website cookies:** These cookies are strictly necessary to provide you with services available through our websites and to use some of its features, such as access to secure areas.

| 

Beachbody

| 

Because these cookies are strictly necessary to deliver the websites to you, you cannot refuse them.

You can block or delete them by changing your browser settings as described below under the heading " _How can I control cookies?_ "  
  
 **Performance and functionality cookies:** These cookies are used to enhance the performance and functionality of our websites, but are non-essential to their use. However, without these cookies, certain functionality may become unavailable.

| 

Tealium; Bazaarvoice; Chartbeat; Google; Facebook; NewRelic; JQuery

| 

To learn how to potentially refuse these cookies, please see the instructions below under the heading " _How can I control cookies?_ "

Alternatively, you can visit these third parties’ websites to learn more, and if offered, opt out of their cookies: Tealium ( _<http://tealium.com/privacy>_ ); Bazaarvoice ( _<http://www.bazaarvoice.com/privacy-policy>_ ); Chartbeat ( _<https://chartbeat.com/privacy/>_ ); Google ( _<https://www.google.com/settings/ads/plugin>_ ); Facebook ( _<https://www.facebook.com/help/cookies/>_ ); New Relic ( _<https://docs.newrelic.com/docs/browser/new-relic-browser/page-load-timing-resources/new-relic-cookies-used-browser>_ )  
  
 **Analytics and customisation cookies:** These cookies collect information that is used either in aggregate form to help us understand how our websites are being used or how effective our marketing campaigns are, or to help us customise our websites for you.

| 

Tealium; Omniture/Adobe; Lytics; Google/YouTube; Facebook; Twitter; Marin Conversion Tag; Quantcast Tag; Tag 4 Arm

| 

To learn how to potentially refuse these cookies, please see the instructions below under the heading " _How can I control cookies?_ "

Alternatively, you can visit these third parties’ websites to learn more, and if offered, opt out of their cookies: Tealium ( _<http://tealium.com/privacy>_ ); Omniture/Adobe ( _<http://www.adobe.com/privacy/opt-out.html>_ ); Lytics ( _<https://www.getlytics.com/privacy>_ ); Google/YouTube ( _<https://www.google.com/settings/ads/plugin>_ ); Facebook ( _<https://www.facebook.com/help/cookies/>_ ); Twitter ( _<https://support.twitter.com/articles/20170514>_ ); Marin Conversion Tag ( _<http://insights.marinsoftware.com/facebook/migrate-new-facebook-conversion-pixel/>_ ); Quantcast Tag ( _<https://www.quantcast.com/wp-content/uploads/2011/05/Publisher_Book.pdf>_ )  
  
 **Advertising cookies:** These cookies are used to make advertising messages more relevant to you. They perform functions like preventing the same ad from continuously reappearing, ensuring that ads are properly displayed for advertisers, and in some cases selecting advertisements that are based on your interests.

| 

Google; Connexity; Tealium; AddThis; Adsymptotic; DoubleClick; Adsrvr; Pinterest; Bing.com; Yahoo Dot (Gemini); Steel House 

| 

To learn how to potentially refuse these cookies, please see the instructions below under the heading " _How can I control cookies?_ "

Alternatively, you can visit these third parties’ websites to learn more, and if offered, opt out of their cookies: Google ( _<https://www.google.com/settings/ads/plugin>_ ); Connexity ( _<https://connexity.com/gb/opt-out>_ ); Tealium ( _<http://tealium.com/privacy>_ ); AddThis ( _<http://www.addthis.com/privacy/opt-out>_ ); DoubleClick (<https://support.google.com/dfp_premium/answer/2839090?hl=en>); Adsrvr ( _<http://www.adsrvr.org/opt-out.html>_ ); Pinterest ( _<https://help.pinterest.com/en/help-topic/Legal%20and%20privacy>_ ); Yahoo Dot ( _<https://gemini.yahoo.com/advertiser/home>_ ); Steel House ( _<https://help.steelhouse.com/hc/en-us/articles/204185005-What-Is-The-SteelHouse-Smarter-Pixel->_ )  
  
 **Social networking cookies:** These cookies are used to enable you to share pages and content that you find interesting on our websites through third party social networking and other websites. These cookies may also be used for advertising purposes too.

| 

Google/YouTube; Facebook; Twitter

| 

To learn how to potentially refuse these cookies, please see the instructions below under the heading " _How can I control cookies?_ "

Alternatively, you can visit these third parties’ websites to learn more, and if offered, opt out of their cookies: Google/YouTube (<https://www.google.com/settings/ads/plugin>); Facebook (<https://www.facebook.com/help/cookies/>); Twitter (<https://support.twitter.com/articles/20170514>)  
  
 **What About Other Tracking Technologies, Like Web Beacons?**

Cookies are not the only way to recognise or track visitors to a website. We also collect information through the use of other, similar technologies, such as "pixel tags" on our websites and in e-mail messages we may send to you which may be placed by us or a third party with whom we partner. “Pixels”, also known as "Web beacons," are tiny graphic files or code snippets, not visible to the human eye, that can be included in HTML-encoded e-mail messages and web pages. When such a message is opened in an HTML-capable e-mail program, the recipient's computer or device will communicate with our server to retrieve the pixel tag file, allowing us to record and store, along with the recipient's e-mail address, the date and time the recipient viewed the e-mail message, the fact that the recipient's e-mail client is capable of receiving HTML-encoded e-mail, and other standard logging information. The pixel tag may also see or read cookies. Beachbody may use pixel tags in order to measure and understand traffic better, improve site performance, track visitor behavior to improve user experience, and for tracking promotional and marketing campaign response, among others. You can disable the pixel tag feature by changing the settings on your e-mail client to prevent the automatic downloading of images, changing your browser settings to omit images, disabling Javascript, or there are commercial software packages available that can omit pixel tags and most advertisements.

 **Do You Use Flash cookies or Local Shared Objects?**

Our websites may also use so-called "Flash Cookies" (also known as Local Shared Objects or "LSOs") to, among other things, collect and store information about your use of our services, fraud prevention and for other site operations. 

If you do not want Flash Cookies stored on your computer, you can adjust the settings of your Flash player to block Flash Cookies storage using the tools contained in the website Storage Settings Panel. You can also control Flash Cookies by going to the Global Storage Settings Panel and following the instructions (which may include instructions that explain, for example, how to delete existing Flash Cookies (referred to "information" on the Macromedia site), how to prevent Flash LSOs from being placed on your computer without your being asked, and (for Flash Player 8 and later) how to block Flash Cookies that are not being delivered by the operator of the page you are on at the time). 

Please note that setting the Flash Player to restrict or limit acceptance of Flash Cookies may reduce or impede the functionality of some Flash applications, including, potentially, Flash applications used in connection with our services or online content.

 **Do You Serve Targeted Advertising?**

We also work with third parties that use tracking technologies on our websites in order to provide tailored advertisements on our behalf and on behalf of other advertisers across the Internet. These third party partners may place or recognize a unique cookie on your hard drive. Advertisers and third party advertising partners may use third party cookies in order to collect information about you, which may include how many times you have seen their ads or whether you have interacted with an ad. They may also use third party cookies to provide you with interest-based or behavioral advertising. The information collected through this process does not enable us or them to identify your name, contact details or other personally identifying details unless you choose to provide this information. 

**How Can I Control Cookies?**

You can set or amend your web browser controls to accept or reject cookies. If you choose to reject cookies, you may still use our websites, however your access to some functionality and areas of our website may be severely restricted. 

  * **_Browser Controls_** : Most major web browsers provide users with the option to accept or reject cookies. Opting out relies on information in the unique cookies placed on your web browser by our partners, so if you delete cookies, use a different device, or change web browsers, you may need to opt out again. Please note that if you use your browser settings to block all cookies you may not be able to access parts of our or others' websites. The “Help” feature on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. Additionally, you can disable or delete similar data used by browser add-ons, such as Flash cookies, by changing the add-on's settings or visiting the website of its developer. Since cookies allow you to take advantage of some of our essential features, we recommend that you leave them turned on. For instance, if you block or otherwise reject our cookies, you may not be able to utilize certain critical features on our websites, such as adding items to your shopping cart, proceeding to checkout, or using essential features or services that require you to sign in.
  *  ** _Disabling Most Targeting or Behavior Advertising Cookies_** : If you would like to disable advertising cookies which remember your browsing habits and display relevant advertising when you use our websites or any Beachbody Services, or to more generally understand your options, please visit _[http://www.youronlinechoices.com](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/)_ or the Network Advertising Initiative at _[www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/)_. If you choose to turn off these cookies, you will still be served with advertisements on the Internet, but it may not be tailored to your interests. Whilst many companies involved in using advertising cookies and serving online behavioural advertising appear at the links above, not all do, so please remember that even if you choose to turn off cookies used by all of the companies listed, you may still receive some advertising cookies and some tailored advertisements from other companies. 
  * **_Targeted Advertising; Do Not Track Signals_** : We may customize content and advertisements for our products and services on our websites or mobile applications in order to make the content and advertising as informative and useful to you as possible. We do this by using information that you provide to us or we obtain through tracking technologies. To prevent this, some web browsers offer a “Do Not Track” signal that is a HTTP header field indicating your preference regarding tracking or cross-site user tracking. Like many other websites and online services, we do not currently alter our practices when we receive Do Not Track signals as there is no consensus among industry participants as to what "Do Not Track" means in this context. To find out more about "Do Not Track," you may wish to visit _<http://www.allaboutdnt.com/>_. 

**How Often Will You Update This Cookie Statement?**

We may update this Cookie Notice from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to the cookies we use or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons. Please re-visit this Cookie Notice regularly to stay informed about our use of cookies and related technologies. 

**Where Can I Get Further Information?**

If you have any questions about our use of cookies or other technologies, please email us at _[Privacy@Beachbody.com](mailto:Privacy@Beachbody.com)_.
